

## KANIKA SALUJA Finance Associate

### **Professional Goals**

Enterprising, hard-working and technically skilled account specialist known for accuracy, attention to detail and timeliness in managing disbursement functions for diverse- industry employers. A/P career span 3.5 years of experience in telecom industry and has included accountability for the processing of up to 5,000 invoices (1M) per month. Backed by solid credentials (BS in accounting) and proficiencies in generally accepted accounting practices as well as MS Office Suite, Busy, Tally ERP, EDMS, Google sheets and Genisys.

### Get in touch!

## Mobile: +919717131998

# Email:

kanika\_saluja07@yahoo.com

#### **Education:**

Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning, Pune-2020 MBA

Delhi University-2014 B.Com

# Date of Birth: 25-Sep-1991

City: Dehi

#### Keyskills:

- Advance Excel, Account Reconciliation Processes
  Vendor Management & Negotations
- Tally ERP9 & Tally 9.0
- Corporate Accounting & Bookkeeping
- Invoices/Expense Reports/Payment Transactions
- Records Organizations & Management Spreadsheets & Accounting Reports

### Work Experience

### **Accounts Associate**

Lash Technologies Pvt Ltd | Sep 2022 - Aug 2023

- Compiling and reviewing financial information.
- Preparing financial forms, documents and reports.
- Assisting with preparation of budgets and financial statement of marketing campaigns.
- Ensure campaigns are executed on time with budget and to a high standard of quality.
- Assisting with tax filing, accounts receivables, accounts payables and payroll processing.
- Maintaining records and filing systems.
- Reconcile the Banking Transactions.

#### **Accounts Receivable**

Sri Amarnath Finance Ltd I Dec 2017 - Jan 2022

- Maintain precise records of all incoming payments.
- Receiving and processing daily cheque deposits.
- Contact clients as needed to ensure payments of outstanding invoices.
- Reconcile any irregularities in receipts.
- Work collaboratively with accounts payable and other accounting staff to ensure accuracy in finances.
- Generate and deliver reports to different departments as needed.
- Actively investigate and resolve irregularities in both incoming and outgoing payments.

### Accounts Payable

Mynd Solutions Pvt Ltd | Apr 2014 - Dec 2017

- Addressed escalated issues from employees and vendors.
- Resolving Vendor Queries via Emails as per TAT.
- Creating PAN India MIS, Dashboard and Rejection MIS reports as per agreed SLA.
- Weekly review with Management.
- Resolving Invoice Processing and Payment escalations.